



I am an established technical lead with an entrepreneurial mindset. I have over nine years of experience generating, sharing and enhancing software. As a person who values the collaborative aspects of coding, I am always looking for creative ways to contribute towards and invest in prompt and successful projects.

#### Education

B.A. in Multidisciplinary Studies: Specializing in Computer Science, Digital Art and Electronic Music State University of New York at Stony Brook • 2018

A.A.S. in Information Technology

Suffolk County Community College • 2014

#### Skills

**Programming**: Typescript, Python, C++, Java

Web: Next.js (React), Angular, Webpack, WebAssembly

**Environments & Runtimes**: Kubernetes / Docker Swarm, NodeJS, Linux & MacOS **Integration & Management**: Github Actions, Github Packages, NPM, TravisCI, Ansible

Databases & datastores: MongoDB Atlas and PostGreSQL, BigQuery, Redis

**Cloud**: Google Cloud (GKE, Cloud Functions & VPC), Amazon Web Services, (Fargate, Lambda)

Machine Learning: Kubeflow, Keras (TensorFlow), PyTorch

Productivity Software: FFMPEG & ImageMagick, Adobe Creative Suite, Jira, Git, Postman, LucidChart

# **Experience**

#### Binox MSP, Garden City NY

2019 - 2023

Co-founder and Chief Technology Officer

- × Successfully produced the MVP for a modern PaaS (Platform as a Service) application to synchronize data in realtime between PSA (Professional Service Automation) and CRM softwares.
- × Interacted directly with corporate customers as the face of the product, collecting feedback from them and ensuring that their expectations were met.
- × Lead and trained a small tightly-knit team of remote developers in Latin America to scale the codebase and deploy it onto serverless functions.
- × Selected effective cloud native technologies to capitalize on revolutionary advancements in cost optimized computing.
- × Thoroughly documented the architecture of the product from top to bottom, both within the code directly and externally through graphical presentations.
- × Provisioned a document database cluster with multiple shards capable of handling the types of high frequency transactions associated with realtime sync.
- × Formed a close relationship with different API vendors and consumers to receive, share and automate documentation for REST and GraphQL based services.
- × Generated a pipeline to capture data from syncs and perform ETL (Extract, Transform and Load) operations which yielded automatic corporate performance metrics and dashboards for customers.
- × Pivoted Binox from a single product to a suite of products including a complete standalone CRM.

## **Experience (Continued)**

#### Arts.Codes, Brooklyn NY

2017 - 2019, 2022 [consulting]

## Lead Developer

- × Created and maintained a data driven mixed reality sculptural installation titled háček as commissioned by O'Reilly Media and The Shmoo Security Group, which visualized realtime DDOS attacks executed against their event ticketing systems.
- Vilial visual visual
- × Built and programmed the interactive LED component for a sculptural art piece titled *Verses* comissioned by the federal goverment for installation at their campus in lower manhattan

#### Teaching & Learning Lab, Stonybrook NY

2014 - 2017

## **Project Manager**

- × Contributed towards a custom animation framework designed to accurately represent scientific instruments in online training.
- × Directed the design of a progressive web application to test graduate neurobiology students on the structure of the human brain using synthesized fMRI scans.
- × Managed automated testing and deployment workflows for educational software, including the grading service integrated into other projects.
- × Made a cross platform augmented reality app in the Unity game engine which allowed university students to interact with a projection of the school's mascot *Wolfie* in 3D space and play games written by other students.

# Independent projects & consulting:

# DeepDream Docker API service April 2023

https://github.com/Kezzsim/deepdream-api-docker

Digital preservation of Google's Deep Dream neural network, translating Python 2.7 code to Python 3 and containerizing it with legacy dependancies so it can run on modern systems.

## **Strayve Silent Disco** July 2018

Open Source JavaScript based silent disco app, allowing for performers to spawn spontaneous events in public spaces using only a computer. The audience tunes in via smartphone through an access point reconfigured as a captive portal.

### Mixed Reality Deck at VR World NYC July 2017

Rebuilt camera system for a virtual reality environment which uses chroma keying to display an image of the user overlaid within the game they're playing.